// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the safety sign?",
    immg:"img1",
    answer: "Information Sign",
    options: [
      "Warn Sign",
      "Mandatory Sign",
      "Information Sign",
      "Danger Sign"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is smothering in extinguishing of fire?",
    answer: "Isolating the fire from the supply of oxygen",
    options: [
      "Adding the fuel element to the fire",
      "Removing the fuel element from the fire",
      "Using of water to lower the temperature", 
      "Isolating the fire from the supply of oxygen"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the physical hazard?",
    
    answer: "Vibration",
    options: [
      "Smoking",
      "Vibration",
      "Corrosive",
      "Radio Active"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which is the correct sequence of operation to be performed when using the fire extinguisher?",
    answer: "Pull, Aim, Squeeze,Sweep",
    options: [
      "Pull, Aim, Squeeze,Sweep",
      "Pull, Aim, Sweep,Squeeze",
      "Push, Arrange,Squeeze, Sweep ",
      "Push, Arrange,Sweep, Sequence"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which step of the 5s-concept refers 'Standardization' ?",
    answer: "Step-4",
    options: [
      "Step-1",
      "Step-2",
      "Step-3",
      "Step-4"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which plier is used for making wire hooks and loops?",
    answer: "Round nose plier",
    options: [
      "Flat nose plier",
      "Long nose plier",
      "Round nose plier",
      "Diagonal cutting plier"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the use of pincer? ",
    answer: "Extracting the pin nails from the wood",
    options: [
      "Twisting the flexible wires ",
      "Cutting small diameter of wires",
      "Extracting the pin nails from the wood",
      "Holding small objects, where fing"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "  What is the name of road safety sign? ",
    immg:"img8",
    answer: "Mandatory sign",
    options: [
      "Mandatory sign",
      "Cautionary sign",
      "Informatory sign ",
      "Prohibition sign"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " What is the back ground colour of warning signs in the basic category?  ",
  
    answer: "Yellow",
    options: [
      "Blue",
      "White",
      "Yellow",
      "Green"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which type of fire extinguisher is used for fire on electrical equipment?  ",
  
    answer: "Halon Type",
    options: [
      "Halon Type",
      "Foam Type,
      "Gas catridge type",
      "Stored Pressure type"
    ]
  },
 {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which is the waste disposal method that produces heat?",
  
    answer: "Incineration",
    options: [
      "Recycling",
      "Compositing",
      "Incineration",
      "Waste compaction"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Which Personal Protective Equipment (PPE) is used for the protection from fumes?",
  
    answer: "Nose Mask",
    options: [
      "Apron",
      "Goggles",
      "Ear Mask",
      "Nose Mask"
    ]
  },
    
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
